<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KARINBERG</title>
    <link>https://karinberg.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KARINBERG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:27:12 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://karinberg.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>flygge - Your camper navi</title>
      <link>https://karinberg.github.io/projects/project4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:27:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinberg.github.io/projects/project4/</guid>
      <description>Short description:
flygge is a navigation app for motorhome drivers.
If you want to navigate your motorhome today, you have the choice between free generic apps like Google Maps or expensive special apps with way too many features that are not useful for most campers. flygge is different: The first motorhome navigation focused on easy travel. Thanks to its own camper dimensions, live traffic or the special route guidance especially for your camper, flygge makes it easy for you to get to your destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://karinberg.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 17:27:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinberg.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Karin
I am currently working part-time as a freelance mobile developer and DevOps Engineer. The other part I work as DevOps engineer for Mobisys.
My background is diverse (you could say I&amp;rsquo;m a specialized generalist), but always close to coding. I have done a bit of everything, from backend development to mobile apps and devops topics.
I love automation as a way to optimize processes and avoid repetitive work, and working in happy agile teams - where work is a way to design beautiful products that solve a problem, and not a mean by itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://karinberg.github.io/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 17:27:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinberg.github.io/experience/</guid>
      <description>Over 18 years of experience working in all kind of project sizes and teams. I have developed digital products to help businesses and improve people&amp;rsquo;s lives, solving complex problems with simple solutions.
2021 - now: Mobile Apps Developer + DevOps Engineer, Freelancer
2022 - now: DevOps Engineer, Mobisys GmbH
2019 - 2021: Mobile Apps Developer + DevOps Engineer (iOS, Android, Xamarin, Azure), Daimler-Truck AG
2015 - 2019: Mobile Apps Developer (iOS, Android, Xamarin), Daimler-Fleetboard GmbH</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Binding library for HEREMaps</title>
      <link>https://karinberg.github.io/projects/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 17:27:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinberg.github.io/projects/project2/</guid>
      <description>Short description:
Xamarin Binding library to make HEREMaps Premium Edition SDKs (v.3.15) available for Xamarin.iOS and Xamarin.Android Apps. Latest project which tries to use the native iOS and Android HEREMaps SDK inside of an Xamarin app. First version looks promesing but I&amp;rsquo;m still in testing phase :)
Learn more and contribute on GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft AppCenter Exporter</title>
      <link>https://karinberg.github.io/projects/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 17:27:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinberg.github.io/projects/project3/</guid>
      <description>Short description:
Prometheus exporter for Microsoft AppCenter information e.g. the ui test runs. This project is a copy of the Azure DevOps Exporter which I adjusted to scrape information from the Microsoft AppCenter instead of MicrosoftAzure DevOps. We use it to alert us in case of failing ui tests of our apps.
Learn more and contribute on GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iCashBox - From idea to App Store in 48 hours</title>
      <link>https://karinberg.github.io/projects/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 17:27:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinberg.github.io/projects/project1/</guid>
      <description>iOS Mobile App: iCashBox
App idea: The basic idea was to develop an app with which it is possible to manage a holiday fund or similar. Think of the next skiing holiday, for example. 5 people go skiing together and each one throws 100 € into the holiday fund to pay for food, petrol, etc. This app should help you to keep track of the expenses and receipts of each person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s connect</title>
      <link>https://karinberg.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinberg.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You have a project you would like to implement? You have a developer team that needs support?
Contact me at hello(at)karinberg.de</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
